<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wish You Were Beer!</title>
    <link>https://wishbeer.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Wish You Were Beer!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wishbeer.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TweetBot&#39;a Veda!</title>
      <link>https://wishbeer.github.io/posts/2023/01/tweetbota-veda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wishbeer.github.io/posts/2023/01/tweetbota-veda/</guid>
      <description>Twitter&amp;rsquo;a 2008 yılında kaydolmuşum. O yıllarda sosyal medya daha yeni oluşmaya başlıyordu ve Twitter&amp;rsquo;daki tek amac o an ne yaptığını bildirmekten ibaretti.
Yıllar geçtikçe işler değişti, Twitter büyüdü, artık takip edilmeyen hesapları bile size zorla göstermeye, aralara reklamlar almaya başladı.
İşte o zamanlar Twitter&amp;rsquo;a sadece kendi timeline&amp;rsquo;ınıza ulaşmayı sağlayan programlar yaygınlaşmaya başladı. Echofon, Twitterrific, Tweetie&amp;hellip;ve TweetBot!
Sadece takip ettiklerimi göstermesi ve reklamları timeline&amp;rsquo;ımın dışında tutması ile TweetBot 2011 yılından beri hem telefonumda hem de bilgisayarımda kullandığım bir program olmuştu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caret</title>
      <link>https://wishbeer.github.io/posts/2022/12/caret/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wishbeer.github.io/posts/2022/12/caret/</guid>
      <description>Nedense Markdown editor&amp;rsquo;lere karşın bir zaafım var. MacBook kullandığım zamanlarda OmmWriter ile başladığım süreçte daha sonra Byword kullandım. Son zamanlarda Ulysses ile devam ediyorum.
Windows bu alanda program bulması daha zor bir platform olmuştur. Zaman zaman çeşitli programları denedim ancak hiçbir zaman istediğim özelliklere sahip doğru düzgün çalışan bir program bulamadım.
Caret ise yıllardır bulamadığım cevher oldu benim için. Hemen hemen aradığım tüm özelliklere sahip, fazlasıyla stabil ve kullanması gayet keyifli.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wish You Were Beer</title>
      <link>https://wishbeer.github.io/posts/2022/12/wish-you-were-beer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wishbeer.github.io/posts/2022/12/wish-you-were-beer/</guid>
      <description>Try to create a nice blog with Hugo. Name fits right&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ses Kartları Hakkında</title>
      <link>https://wishbeer.github.io/posts/2022/12/ses-kartlar%C4%B1-hakk%C4%B1nda/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wishbeer.github.io/posts/2022/12/ses-kartlar%C4%B1-hakk%C4%B1nda/</guid>
      <description>Bilgisayarlardaki ses sistemleri yıllardır ilgimi çekmiş, üzerlerinde sayısız araştırma yapmışımdır ancak bilgilerim hala fazlasıyla yüzeyseldir. Her yıl belli zamanlarda biraz nostalji yaparak eski bilgisayarlar, ses kartları, grafik kartları, oyunlar hakkında tekrar tekrar araştırma yapar bildiklerimi tekrar tekrar yeniden öğrenirim.
Ses kartları üzerinde çok çalıştım, özellikle Sound Blaster ve modelleri hakkında. Pek çok ince detayı biliyor olmama karşın internetteki bilgi kirliliği, kimi anlatımların tam doğru yerine dolaylı olarak açıklanması sebebiyle pek çok şeyi yalan yanlış öğrenmiş bulunmaktayım.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>https://wishbeer.github.io/posts/2014/09/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wishbeer.github.io/posts/2014/09/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>https://wishbeer.github.io/posts/2014/03/migrate-to-hugo-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wishbeer.github.io/posts/2014/03/migrate-to-hugo-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Création d&#39;un nouveau thème</title>
      <link>https://wishbeer.github.io/posts/2014/09/cr%C3%A9ation-dun-nouveau-th%C3%A8me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wishbeer.github.io/posts/2014/09/cr%C3%A9ation-dun-nouveau-th%C3%A8me/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Ce tutoriel vous montrera comment créer un thème simple pour Hugo. Je suppose que vous êtes familier avec HTML, la ligne de commande bash, et que vous êtes à l&amp;rsquo;aise avec Markdown pour formater le contenu. Je vais expliquer comment Hugo utilise des modèles et comment vous pouvez organiser vos modèles pour créer un thème. Je ne couvrirai pas l&amp;rsquo;utilisation de CSS pour styliser votre thème.
Nous allons commencer par créer un nouveau site avec un modèle très basique.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://wishbeer.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wishbeer.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is the world’s fastest framework for building websites. It is written in Go.
It makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.com/russross/blackfriday https://github.com/alecthomas/chroma https://github.com/muesli/smartcrop https://github.com/spf13/cobra https://github.com/spf13/viper Learn more and contribute on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>https://wishbeer.github.io/posts/2014/04/hugo-template-primer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wishbeer.github.io/posts/2014/04/hugo-template-primer/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent Go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in Go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using Go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Débuter avec Hugo</title>
      <link>https://wishbeer.github.io/posts/2014/04/d%C3%A9buter-avec-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wishbeer.github.io/posts/2014/04/d%C3%A9buter-avec-hugo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;étape-1-installer-hugo&#34;&gt;Étape 1. Installer Hugo&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Allez sur la page de téléchargements de
&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/spf13/hugo/releases&#34;&gt;hugo&lt;/a&gt; et téléchargez la version
appropriée à votre système d&amp;rsquo;exploitation et votre architecture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sauvegardez le fichier téléchargé à un endroit précis, afin de l&amp;rsquo;utiliser dans
l&amp;rsquo;étape suivante.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Des informations plus complètes sont disponibles sur la page
&lt;a href=&#34;https://wishbeer.github.io/overview/installing/&#34;&gt;installing hugo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
